hdwallpapersin.com 2014-02-09

# PrivacyPolicy

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is importance to us here at hdwallpapersin.com. Rest assured that any information you provide will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. This policy may be updated or changed anytime and we encourage you to review it whenever you visit the site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

 **Collection and Use of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information such as names and email addresses only when voluntarily submitted. These information are used merely to fulfill a specific request, for example, to post a comment on our blog, to create an account in our Forum, or to subscribe to our mailing list. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further communications.

 **Distribution of Information**

We never use or share any of those information in ways unrelated to the ones described above. We do not send spam and we do not sell your information to any company for marketing purposes. We may, however, share information with government agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

 **Third-Party Advertisers**

In order to cover the costs of providing hdwallpapersin.com as a free resource to the public, we have relationships with many third-party advertising networks. The practices of our advertising partners are not directly covered by hdwallpapersin.com's privacy policy. We recommend that you read their policies. For your convenience we provide a list our advertising partners below. Unfortunately we cannot guarantee it is always comprehensive and up to date.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on hdwallpapersin.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

 **Double Click DART Cookies**

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising. This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Hollywood, you may see Hollywood  hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx. You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Tribal Fusion:Tribal Fusion cookies do NOT collect personally identifiable information.

 **Links to other Websites**

Our site may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you use these links to leave our site, we do not anymore have control over that website. Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement and we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you provide to those sites. Exercise caution and read the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Account Cancellation**

Upon request, your hdwallpapersin.com account can be canceled. Your user profile will no longer appear on the web site and your submissions will no longer be listed publicly for download. Any comments you have posted will still appear and include your username, but will not be linked to your profile. After cancellation, you will be not be available for log-in.

 **Data Retention**

The data submitted to and generated by this web site may be copied to additional machines for redundancy and backup purposes.

 **Privacy Contact Information**

Should you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us using our Contact Form or email us directly at [privacy@hdwallpapersin.com](mailto:privacy@hdwallpapersin.com "Privacy Policy").
